<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>demo on MayJuun</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/categories/demo/</link><description>Recent content in demo on MayJuun</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 05:07:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mayjuun.com/categories/demo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PRAPARE Survey</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/2-prapare-survey/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 05:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/2-prapare-survey/</guid><description>PRAPARE SURVEY - This is an open-source work in progress. The Protocol for Responding to and Assessing Patients&amp;rsquo; Assets, Risks, and Experiences (PRAPARE) survey was recreated in a Flutter environment using its [LOINC FHIR速 specification]. The app directly loads the FHIR速 spec (albeit with some basic modifications to the original FHIR速 JSON to more closely match the initial survey). It has basic validation in place for survey completion.
Features Personal Characteristics Personal Characteristics, filled out Social and Emotional Health</description></item><item><title>AMIA Symptom Tracker</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/1-symptom-tracker/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 04:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/1-symptom-tracker/</guid><description>AMIA Symptom Tracker - This was the demo application used for live-coding in the 4-hour Flutter workshop given at AMIA&amp;rsquo;s 2020 Virtual Clinical Informatics Conference. A total of 6 informaticians hosted this workshop.
Features Welcome Screen, live-coded in full Symptom Tracker Dashboard, live-coded in full Check-In Screen, live-coded in full Firebase Puns, created by audience using Live Share Flutter / Firebase connection, previously created while live-coding FHIR速 Package Demo, creating live patients on HAPI and Aidbox FHIR servers.</description></item></channel></rss>