<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MayJuun</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/</link><description>Recent content on MayJuun</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 13:18:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mayjuun.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>See you at CIVITAS '23!</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/10-civitas-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 17:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/10-civitas-23/</guid><description>CIVITAS Heading to the CIVITAS 2023 Annual Conference this year?
We are honored to be involved in one of the most anticipated events of the year – bringing together the Civitas Networks for Health national network to collaborate and transform the health of our communities.
Join Our Mailing List We&amp;#39;d love to connect. First Name Last Name Organization Title Email Phone Comments Submit</description></item><item><title>See you at HIMSS '23!</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/09-himss-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 17:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/09-himss-23/</guid><description>Interoperability First Heading to HIMSS (Healthcare Information and Management Systems Society) this year?
MayJuun is partnering with Open City Labs to demonstrate the entire closed-loop referral process, from person identification and screening assessment to creating and managing referrals.
We have also partnered with the Interoperability Institute to connect our questionnaire assessments application (Cuestionario) to their MELD open-source sandbox.
Join Our Mailing List We&amp;#39;d love to connect. First Name Last Name Organization Title Email Phone Comments Submit</description></item><item><title>Demos</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/demos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 18:02:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/demos/</guid><description>Recetario Before a patient can complete a Task, it has to be assigned to them. Recetario is our lightweight app that can be integrated into your EHR, to allow clinicians to quickly and easily select Forms, Surveys, and Questionnaires, and send them to the patient to be completed. FHIRPath FHIRPath is a powerful path based navigation and extraction language that is used to power much of our work, including scoring in Questionnaires.</description></item><item><title>NJ InCK HealthStory</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/06-radford-ems/privacy-notice/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 13:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/06-radford-ems/privacy-notice/</guid><description/></item><item><title>NJ InCK HealthStory</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/06-radford-ems/eula/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 13:19:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/06-radford-ems/eula/</guid><description/></item><item><title>MayJuun Apps</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/policies/cookie-policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:01:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/policies/cookie-policy/</guid><description/></item><item><title>MayJuun Apps</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/policies/disclaimer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/policies/disclaimer/</guid><description/></item><item><title>MayJuun Apps</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/policies/eula/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/policies/eula/</guid><description/></item><item><title>MayJuun Apps</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/policies/privacy-notice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/policies/privacy-notice/</guid><description/></item><item><title>MayJuun Apps</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/policies/terms-and-conditions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/policies/terms-and-conditions/</guid><description/></item><item><title>MayJuun Connect - Add Contacts via QR Code</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/08-mayjuun-connect/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:07:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/08-mayjuun-connect/</guid><description>Intro - When flying to a conference, I had inspiration to optimize the means by which my contact information is shared with others. Building apps like these are well within our wheelhouse at MayJuun, and this step seemed like a nice upgrade from the basic business card.
Credit where it&amp;rsquo;s due, this app builds heavily upon the open-source (MIT License) QR Code generator library called Project Nayuki. I&amp;rsquo;ve used their code-generator in a number of projects and recommend them highly.</description></item><item><title>SDC Workflow Example</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/7-sdc-workflow-example/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 03:11:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/7-sdc-workflow-example/</guid><description>Structured Data Capture (SDC) As usual, the HL7 website has a lot to say on the topic of SDC, and I DO advise you to read through it because it&amp;rsquo;s very helpful. However, where I thought I might be able value is with some additional examples.
All of these examples are from a project I&amp;rsquo;m currently involved with for New Jersey Integrated Care for Kids. The idea behind this project is that a clinician (social worker, teacher, etc.</description></item><item><title>ACEP emPOC</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/04-acep-empoc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:07:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/04-acep-empoc/</guid><description>ACEP emPOC - The American College of Emergency Physicians (ACEP) Emergency Medicine Point of Care (emPOC) app is a cross platform application designed to provide evidence-based, Emergency Medicine clinical content in a point-of-care tool designed for use at the bedside. Content within this app is curated from the field&amp;rsquo;s top experts and thought leaders. A web version of this content is available separately on ACEP&amp;rsquo;s website.
For the Android and iOS Flutter release of emPOC (Dec &amp;lsquo;21), we rebuilt emPOC from scratch in collaboration with ACEP&amp;rsquo;s staff.</description></item><item><title>WVEMS Protocols</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/03-wvems-protocols/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 22:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/solutions/03-wvems-protocols/</guid><description>2023 Update - This solution was featured as part of the Nov 2022 IHE USA Path to Production series (#6). That video is available here:
WVEMS Protocols - The WVEMS Protocols app is a cross-platform Flutter app designed to quickly view, interact, and search through PDFs. It is being used clinically in 7 cities and 12 counties in southwest Virginia. The app allows EMTs to access the guidelines and protocols necessary for on-shift patient care.</description></item><item><title>WVEMS Protocols - Interactive, Searchable PDFs</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/07-wvems-protocols/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 20:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/07-wvems-protocols/</guid><description>Intro - Today (Oct 5, 2021), we at MayJuun are proud to officially release the WVEMS Protocols Flutter app on the Apple App Store and the Google Play Store.
This was a wonderful project built in collaboration with the Western Virginia Emergency Medical Services Council, Inc, who provides Emergency Medical Services (EMS) in the state of Virginia&amp;hellip;specificially in the following 7 cities:
Covington Danville Martinsville Radford Roanoke Salem and 12 counties:</description></item><item><title>My First FHIR/Flutter App</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/1-first-fhir-flutter-app/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/1-first-fhir-flutter-app/</guid><description>How To Start Link to full Github Code
For this, I am going to assume that you already know how to install flutter, dart and VS Code (or android studio) on your computer. If not, there are many good tutorials - many found on this very website. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have it, go get it, then you can come back here.
Following these instructions here, I first created the basic flutter application.</description></item><item><title>Azure FHIR® Setup</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/6-azure_fhir_setup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:55:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/6-azure_fhir_setup/</guid><description>Azure FHIR® Setup Some of you may need to use the Azure FHIR® server (my apologies in advance, it cost me $80 over two weeks and then I was like, screw this). However, before I canceled it, I did manage to get authentication to work. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure all of the settings I&amp;rsquo;ve used are required, but this is what I needed to get it to work properly (why is authentication such a pain in the ass?</description></item><item><title>Questionnaires and Surveys</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/5-questionnaires-and-surveys/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:55:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/5-questionnaires-and-surveys/</guid><description>FHIR® Questionnaire As usual, the FHIR® documentation, while complete, is difficult to get through in order to understand how to structure surveys. John has created a really nice demo app to render the Prapare® Survey specifically (https://github.com/FireJuun/prapare). There is also now a very nice dynamic renderer package called Faiadashu, thanks Tilo!
I&amp;rsquo;m also working on creating surveys from a REDCap library, and also from a spreadsheet, but those are works in progress.</description></item><item><title>Flutter Servers</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/4-flutter-servers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/4-flutter-servers/</guid><description>This is a reproduction of the readme from the repo here. Have you ever wanted to try and host your Flutter web app but weren&amp;rsquo;t sure how to do it? I like Dart and Flutter, and didn&amp;rsquo;t want to have to learn another language just to have a web server. Luckily, there are a couple of packages that already have this functionality. I&amp;rsquo;ve just detailed how they work, and how they can be placed in a docker container for easy deployment (including on Google Cloud!</description></item><item><title>Fish and Flutter: 5 Step Install</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/06-fish-and-flutter/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 14:04:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/06-fish-and-flutter/</guid><description>Intro - This is a supplemental post to the YouTube video tutorial that shows how to install iTerm, Fish, and Flutter on a Mac.
The video boils everything down to 5 steps, which I will define here.
Step 1: Homebrew + Fish + iTerm2 To get started, you need to follow the Automatic Installation steps on my iterm-fish-fisher repo, or you can just copy/paste the same steps that are listed below.</description></item><item><title>Podcasting in an Open-Source Era</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/05-podcasting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 15:42:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/05-podcasting/</guid><description>Intro - Well, I can&amp;rsquo;t say this is something I&amp;rsquo;ll do with frequency, so I might as well write about this path on the meta-blog. We created an informatics podcast recently, available here. From the time we recorded the original podcast to the time we had all steps/automation established, we unfortunately found ourselves in a position of needing to rebrand.
Looking back, this proved most beneficial, as it forced me to reflect on the steps I previously took to create a podcast that harnesses GitHub and Hugo for its RSS feeds.</description></item><item><title>pdf2json: A Step-by-Step Guide</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/04-pdf-2-json/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 02:44:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/04-pdf-2-json/</guid><description>Intro - Well, I can&amp;rsquo;t say this issue will come up too often for others&amp;hellip;but should you ever need it, here are the exact steps you can take to convert all the text from a PDF file into a JSON file with key-value pairs of &amp;quot;page#&amp;quot; : &amp;quot;all page text without extra white space&amp;quot;. Note that page# is an integer that starts at 1, not 0.
I needed this in a project where the Flutter packages that performed PDF search functions were not performant, had memory leaks, or seemed to work inconsistently across platforms.</description></item><item><title>Bucket List Accomplished! My First Meta-Blog Post</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/03-bucket-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 23:55:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/03-bucket-list/</guid><description>Intro - My First Meta-Blog Post!
This has been a challenge to get to this point, and hopefully I haven&amp;rsquo;t corrupted the entire website, but here is my first post. This is really more of a test of my ability in GIT to make the changes from my fork and create a pull request to upate the changes. Sounds easy, right? Not so much&amp;hellip;after watching the intro video, I knew I was in for a challenge because I didn&amp;rsquo;t understand alot of the terminology or have a &amp;lsquo;favorite code editor&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>GCP Healthcare API Part 1: Creating FHIR® Store</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/2-gcp-fhir-flutter-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 15:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/2-gcp-fhir-flutter-1/</guid><description>Creating FHIR Store I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on athentication and authorization for FHIR® (including SMART, although not solely). And like so many things, it seems harder than it should be. Google has been giving me problems, so as I work through it, I&amp;rsquo;m going to document my steps, in the hope it will help me (and maybe someone else) in the future.
The first step is that you have to sign up for Google Cloud Platform (oh yeah, while I really like Google&amp;rsquo;s tools, they&amp;rsquo;re not paying me anything).</description></item><item><title>GCP Healthcare API Part 2: Attempting Authentication</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/3-gcp-fhir-flutter-2-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 15:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/fhirfli/3-gcp-fhir-flutter-2-/</guid><description>GCP Healthcare API - Attempting Authentication Again, I&amp;rsquo;ve found this to be tricky, hence why I&amp;rsquo;m documenting here, to hopefully make it easier for someone else. Remember, we should now have a FHIR® store. The one I&amp;rsquo;ve setup exists at:
https://healthcare.googleapis.com/v1/projects/fhir-fli/locations/us/datasets/fhir-fli/fhirStores/fhir-fli
So I&amp;rsquo;ve probably thrown these words around and not completely understanding the difference, so, for your edification:
Authentication: who you are Authorization: what you can do Auditing logs: what you did This comes from Google&amp;rsquo;s page on Authentication.</description></item><item><title>Get Fluttered: MVC+S Architecture, Example</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/02-get-fluttered-mvcs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 19:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/02-get-fluttered-mvcs/</guid><description>Intro - To all who watched my original GetFluttered: MVC+S Architecture video, I want to thank you immensely for your patience.
Before making new GetFluttered videos, we wanted to implement:
A means to provide written, supplemental info &amp;hellip; Meta-Blog; A complex, production-level MVC+S example &amp;hellip; PRAPARE app; &amp;amp; A means for others to join / collaborate &amp;hellip; FlutterJuun Slack invite. With these elements now firmly established, it should be easier to follow along with GetFluttered content by comparing simple + complex code examples that achieve the same objective.</description></item><item><title>A Meta-Post for a Meta-Blog</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/01-meta/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 13:15:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/01-meta/</guid><description>Welcome to the Informatics Meta-Blog - Knowledge is power&amp;hellip;and best shared with others. This is the place where any informatician, innovator, or entrepreneur can crowd-source contribute and build upon each others&amp;rsquo; knowledge.
Many of the things I post here will be open-source and moderately technical, but that&amp;rsquo;s only my preference. If there&amp;rsquo;s something else you want to share about healthcare, informatics, innovation, or entrepreneurship, please feel free. Try to add/share some knowledge if you can&amp;hellip;don&amp;rsquo;t just post something that&amp;rsquo;s a shameless plug for your work.</description></item></channel></rss>