<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>networking on MayJuun</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/tags/networking/</link><description>Recent content in networking on MayJuun</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 17:13:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mayjuun.com/tags/networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>See you at CIVITAS '23!</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/10-civitas-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 17:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/10-civitas-23/</guid><description>CIVITAS Heading to the CIVITAS 2023 Annual Conference this year?
We are honored to be involved in one of the most anticipated events of the year – bringing together the Civitas Networks for Health national network to collaborate and transform the health of our communities.
Join Our Mailing List We&amp;#39;d love to connect. First Name Last Name Organization Title Email Phone Comments Submit</description></item><item><title>See you at HIMSS '23!</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/09-himss-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 17:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/09-himss-23/</guid><description>Interoperability First Heading to HIMSS (Healthcare Information and Management Systems Society) this year?
MayJuun is partnering with Open City Labs to demonstrate the entire closed-loop referral process, from person identification and screening assessment to creating and managing referrals.
We have also partnered with the Interoperability Institute to connect our questionnaire assessments application (Cuestionario) to their MELD open-source sandbox.
Join Our Mailing List We&amp;#39;d love to connect. First Name Last Name Organization Title Email Phone Comments Submit</description></item><item><title>MayJuun Connect - Add Contacts via QR Code</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/08-mayjuun-connect/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:07:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/08-mayjuun-connect/</guid><description>Intro - When flying to a conference, I had inspiration to optimize the means by which my contact information is shared with others. Building apps like these are well within our wheelhouse at MayJuun, and this step seemed like a nice upgrade from the basic business card.
Credit where it&amp;rsquo;s due, this app builds heavily upon the open-source (MIT License) QR Code generator library called Project Nayuki. I&amp;rsquo;ve used their code-generator in a number of projects and recommend them highly.</description></item></channel></rss>