<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Meta-Blog on MayJuun</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Meta-Blog on MayJuun</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 02:44:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mayjuun.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>pdf2json: A Step-by-Step Guide</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/5-pdf-2-json/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 02:44:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/5-pdf-2-json/</guid><description>Intro - Well, I can&amp;rsquo;t say this issue will come up too often for others&amp;hellip;but should you ever need it, here are the exact steps you can take to convert all the text from a PDF file into a JSON file with key-value pairs of &amp;quot;page#&amp;quot; : &amp;quot;all page text without extra white space&amp;quot;. Note that page# is an integer that starts at 1, not 0.
I needed this in a project where the Flutter packages that performed PDF search functions were not performant, had memory leaks, or seemed to work inconsistently across platforms.</description></item><item><title>Bucket List Accomplished! My First Meta-Blog Post</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/4-bucket-list/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 23:55:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/4-bucket-list/</guid><description>Intro - My First Meta-Blog Post!
This has been a challenge to get to this point, and hopefully I haven&amp;rsquo;t corrupted the entire website, but here is my first post. This is really more of a test of my ability in GIT to make the changes from my fork and create a pull request to upate the changes. Sounds easy, right? Not so much&amp;hellip;after watching the intro video, I knew I was in for a challenge because I didn&amp;rsquo;t understand alot of the terminology or have a &amp;lsquo;favorite code editor&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>My First FHIR/Flutter App</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/3-first-fhir-flutter-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 03:09:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/3-first-fhir-flutter-app/</guid><description>How To Start Link to full Github Code
For this, I am going to assume that you already know how to install flutter, dart and VS Code (or android studio) on your computer. If not, there are many good tutorials - many found on this very website. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have it, go get it, then you can come back here.
Following these instructions here, I first created the basic flutter application.</description></item><item><title>Get Fluttered: MVC+S Architecture, Example</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/2-get-fluttered-mvcs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 19:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/2-get-fluttered-mvcs/</guid><description>Intro - To all who watched my original GetFluttered: MVC+S Architecture video, I want to thank you immensely for your patience.
Before making new GetFluttered videos, we wanted to implement:
A means to provide written, supplemental info &amp;hellip; Meta-Blog; A complex, production-level MVC+S example &amp;hellip; PRAPARE app; &amp;amp; A means for others to join / collaborate &amp;hellip; FlutterJuun Slack invite. With these elements now firmly established, it should be easier to follow along with GetFluttered content by comparing simple + complex code examples that achieve the same objective.</description></item><item><title>A Meta-Post for a Meta-Blog</title><link>https://mayjuun.com/blog/1-meta-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 13:15:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mayjuun.com/blog/1-meta-post/</guid><description>Welcome to the Informatics Meta-Blog - Knowledge is power&amp;hellip;and best shared with others. This is the place where any informatician, innovator, or entrepreneur can crowd-source contribute and build upon each others' knowledge.
Many of the things I post here will be open-source and moderately technical, but that&amp;rsquo;s only my preference. If there&amp;rsquo;s something else you want to share about healthcare, informatics, innovation, or entrepreneurship, please feel free. Try to add/share some knowledge if you can&amp;hellip;don&amp;rsquo;t just post something that&amp;rsquo;s a shameless plug for your work.</description></item></channel></rss>